Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
How does it feel to be photographed like this?
こうやって撮られてるのってどんな気分?
Is it that close?
そんなに近いんですか?
Is it already close?
もうすでに近い?
Shall we do it around here then?
じゃあこの辺にしますか
My ex-boyfriend took naughty photos with his smartphone.
今まで付き合った彼氏とかに、スマホでエッチな写真を撮られたり
Or something.
とか
No, it's not.
ない ですよ
What would you do if your boyfriend asked you like that?
もし彼氏がそうやって頼んできたらどうします?
Depends if you come.
来た場合による
I see.
なるほどですね
Do you have a boyfriend currently?
今付き合ってる彼氏はいるんですか?
I'm not there.
いないです
How long have you been gone?
どれくらいいないんですか?
It hasn't been that long yet.
まだそんなに経ってないから
Besides, he's still my boyfriend.
別に今はまだ彼氏
By the way, how many people have you experienced so far?
ちなみに今までの経験人数って何人いるんですか?
it is...
それは...
Generally.
一般的に
In general?
一 般的に?
Approximately how many people are there?
だいたい何人いるんですか?
Why is it so appropriate?
なんでそんなに適当なんですか?
almost?
だいたい?
By the way, when was your first meeting?
ちなみに初会見っていつでしたか?
What was the press conference like at that time?
その時の会見は?
There was a press conference.
会見はあったよ
It's close.
近いな
Try not to get too close to it any more.
この以上はあまり近寄らないようにします
Can I have you slowly take off your clothes from the bottom?
服を下からゆっくり脱いでもらっていいですか?
From below?
下から?
What do you mean?
どういうことですか?
all?
全部?
Slowly take off your clothes starting from the bottom and reveal yourself underneath.
下から順番にゆっくり脱いで、下に姿になりましょう
Well...
じゃあ...
So does that mean I should just leave the broser and panties behind?
じゃあブロザーとパンツだけ残さればいいということですか?
that's right.
そうです
Well then, that's fine.
じゃあいいですけど
Do you take that much?
そんなに取るの?
I'll take it.
取ります
No way.
やだよ
I'm just wondering about something else.
今ちょっともうなんかポロッと
Can you see my face?
顔映るんですか?
My face isn't shown.
顔映ってないです
Why?
どうして?
There's no point in showing it too much.
あまり映してもしかない
why?
なんで?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Eh.
えー
It's embarrassing because it's not that big.
そんなに大きくないから恥ずかしい
The shape is so beautiful.
すごい形が綺麗
It's cute.
かわいいよ
Can I touch your pants?
あんたのパンツ触っていい?
what happened?
どうしたの?
My hand moved.
手が動いちゃった
what happened?
どうしたの?
My hand moved.
手が動いちゃった
no,
いや、
It's reflected.
映 るね
It looks great.
めっちゃ映るんだ
Let me show it.
映させて
Look again.
もう一度見て
Will it work if I do this?
こうやったら動くのか?
Like.
みたいな
You don't want to attract attention, do you?
気を見たくないでしょ
I don't know.
わかんない
You look important.
重要な顔してる
This article.
本文
This article is important.
本文重要
What to say
何言
That's it.
って
Let me take a look inside.
中 をちょっと見させて
It's very erotic though.
めっちゃエロいんですけど
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It's cold.
冷たいじゃん
Are you doing it yourself?
自分でやってるの?
this.
これ
It's already here.
もうだし
But when I got my hair removed, it hurt when I bled.
でも脱毛したら血が出たら痛かった
Seriously?
マジで?
You can't do it anymore, right?
もうやんないでしょ
Wait, can I stretch it out?
待って、伸ばしていい?
Both legs.
両足はね
Both legs?
両足?
You can't take it off.
脱げないでしょ
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
You have beautiful legs.
美脚だね
Are you okay.
大丈夫
You're crying.
泣いてるって
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいじゃん
You're being praised.
褒められてるのね
I was praised.
褒められた
Enough is enough?
もういいでいい?
I don't like it.
嫌だね
Do you mean it's embarrassing?
恥ずかしいってこと?
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Very close.
めっちゃ近い
Isn't there a difference?
違くない?
close.
近い
Lend me your hand.
手貸して
hand?
手?
hand
手
in.
で
That's enough.
もう いいよ
Then just leave it like that for a while.
じゃあそのままちょっと
Erotic, stay here.
エロいか、ここにいて
what up?
どう した?
all?
全部?
Where is this?
ここは?
what?
何?
Why?
何で?
Because I want you to see it.
見てほしいから
yes.
そう
What should I do?
どうしよう
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Yeah.
うん
Around?
周り?
I don't understand.
わからないよ
Is it a rim?
リムなの?
That's changing.
変わってるね
Has it changed?
変わってる?
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
TRUE?
本当?
I have 6 cups, right?
私は6杯あるんじゃない?
That's not true.
そんなことないよ
It's coming out really well though.
なんかすごい出てるんだけど
It's kind of amazing.
なんか すごいね
Something has changed a lot.
なんかすごい変わってるよね
I'm a little scared to lick it.
舐めるのはちょっと怖いな
I don't like it.
嫌だわ
It's kind of amazing.
なんかすごい
bad.
まずい
It's already painful.
もう辛い
Interesting
面白
Yes.
い ね
Are you not good at Perachu?
ペラチュウは苦手なの?
Is it fun?
楽しいの?
fun.
楽しい
That's kind of amazing.
なんかすごいね
amazing?
すごい?
What's amazing?
何がすごい?
I'd say it's M-ish.
Mっぽいっていうか
You took a bath, right?
お風呂入ったんだよね
Does it smell like sweat?
汗臭い?
already?
はや?
Are you sweating?
汗かいた?
I was filming it just now.
今撮ってたね
It hurts a little.
ちょっと痛い
sorry.
ごめん
You've lost quite a bit of weight.
結構痩せたね
You lost weight in the bath.
お風呂に痩せたね
Is it good for bathing?
お風呂にいいの?
That's right.
そうだ
You took a bath, right?
お風呂入ったんだよね
Why does it smell like sweat?
なんで汗臭い?
already?
はや?
Are you sweating?
汗かいた?
I was filming it just now.
今撮ってたね
It hurts a little.
ちょっと痛い
sorry.
ごめん
You've lost quite a bit of weight.
結構痩せたね
You've lost so much weight.
そんなに痩せたね
Is it good for bathing?
お風呂にいいの?
yes.
そう
what?
何?
It's M.
Mだね
what?
何?
It's a little disgusting.
ちょっと気持ち悪い
That's disgusting.
そこ気持ち悪い
Things have changed, haven't they?
変わってるよね
That's disgusting.
そこ気持ち悪い
what?
何?
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
Isn't it delicious?
美味しくない?
Strange shape?
変な形?
Someone else?
他の人?
Isn't everyone weird?
み んな変じゃない?
Maybe everyone is weird.
多分みんな変だよね
Have you ever added a day?
一日加えたことあるでしょ?
dislike.
嫌い
Is that so?
そんなの?
Because it's disgusting.
だって気持ち悪いんだもん
Is it that good?
そんなにいいの?
It's pretty close.
結構近いよ
On top?
上に?
Are you going to straddle it?
またがるの?
Have you ever done it?
やったことある?
Not that much.
そんなにないよ
I wish I could go in.
入ればいいけど
I'll go in by myself.
自分で入るから
Did it come out?
抜けた?
Get out
抜 け
Ta.
た
TRUE?
本当?
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいいの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
That's not good.
それは良くないです
behind?
後ろ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Yeah.
うん
That was good.
それで良かった
TRUE?
本当?
It slipped out.
抜けた
Is it okay?
いいの?
It feels good, that.
気持ちいいよ、それ
TRUE?
本当?
I haven't put it out yet.
僕はまだ出してないよ
What are you going to do?
何をやる?
Gas or rather air.
ガスというか空気が
I drank water, head.
水飲んだよ、頭
You got some water out.
水分出したね
It feels so good that it comes out a lot.
気持ちいいからいっぱい出ちゃうんだって
Is that so?
そうなの?
Yes, it's good, isn't it?
そう、いいもんでしょ